<resources>
        <string name="app_name">AboutMe</string>
        <string name="name">Tom Keane</string>
        <string name="yellow_star">Yellow Star</string>
        <string name="what_is_your_nickname">What is your Nickname?</string>
        <string name="bio">
                Recent research physics and software development graduate from Maynooth.
                UNIVERSITY PROJECTS
                \n\n
                •	For my thesis in Theoretical Physics, I created pseudo quantum field in 1+1 dimensions, using Python.
                For this, a lattice model served as a scalar field whose solution was the Klein-Gordon equation. Monte Carlo simulations were used to cause random fluctuations throughout the field, which would create phase transitions.
                The objective of this was to study how these fields would behave in high and low temperature systems.
                \n
                •	In 2018, I worked in a group of three to develop a mobile web-application, StockWatcher. This receives API information from three major stock-market exchanges and displays the information in a user’s account. The app was built on Ionic as a framework, and Angular was used for user authentication. I was responsible for creating Ionic User Authentication forms and handling the users data with FireBase.
                \n
                •	Assignments and Projects: work from Web Information Processing and Algorithms modules are provided on my Github account (linked below).
                for these modules, I have developed:
                \n
                -	A  travelling salesman delivery drone which implements time dependent route prioritisation to optimise efficiency.
                \n
                -	 A web application designed to teach authenticated users the Japanese alphabet ‘Hiragana’ character set. This utilises reactive html features, such as on-scroll Gif events, CSS show/hide options, and user-end quizzes on the Japanese alphabets through javaScript. This project was set up on a XAMPP server.
                \n\n
                •	I have testing experience with Postman, EclEmma and Selenium.
                \n\n
                SIDE PROJECTS
                \n
                •	My Github also showcases many Node.js web applications which I have developed in my own time. These include:
                \n
                -	 chatApp - A single page chat room application on an Express framework. This uses the Node.js WebSocket library, Socket.IO to provide bidirectional communication between client and server.
                \n
                -	todoApp – A REACT application which allows users to create a to-do list.
                \n
                - pitchFinder - an express application which serves as an API for sending geoJSON requests to find the nearest football venue to the user. includes Leaflet mapping and React components.
                \n
        </string>
        <string name="done">done</string>
</resources>
